(忆往昔)
Henry Winchester
Henry Winchester.
他是我们的祖父
That's our grandfather.
你们是学者 对吗
You are men of letters,correct.
我们的父亲教导我们成为猎人的
Our father taught us how to be hunters.
你们是传人
You are legacies.
是旁观这个世界的人
Preceptors,beholders.
记录一切超自然现象的人
Chroniclers of all that which man does not understand.
Larry Ganem和Albert Magus
Larry Ganem and Albert Magnus.
Albertus Magnus
Albertus Magnus.
只是一个隐姓埋名前的化名而已
His was the alias we'd use when going incognito.
我们做个交易
Here's the deal.
你告诉我们怎么样追踪天使
You tell us how to hack an angel.
我就给你点人血
And I'm gonna give you some human blood.
听说你最近对这个很着迷
Word is you're jonesing for it.
地狱骑士可不是随便能杀死的
Knights of hell isn't exactly the dying kind.
但是还有有东西能杀死他们
But there are some can kill a knight.
初刃
The first blade.
是因为那该死的该隐之印
The bloody mark of Cain.
没有这个印记 初刃就毫无用处
Without the mark,the blade is useless.
印记可以转移到值得拥有它的人身上
The mark could be transferred to someone who's worthy.
但是随之而来的负担非常沉重
But you have to know with the mark comes a great burden.
初刃到底在哪里
So where is the blade.
被我扔到大洋的最深处
I threw it to the bottom of the deepest ocean.
你不能到海底下去找 但我可以
You can't search the bottom of the ocean,but I can.
我会找到初刃
So I will find it.
然后把它交给它的新主人
And bring it to its new owner.
如今
Now.
Crowley 接电话
Oh Crowley,pick up.
他到底去哪里了
Where the hell is he.
就好像他有社交生活一样
It's like he's got a social life.
你不会真的在担心吧
What,are you actually worried.
疗伤正忙 无法接应
Too busy of fitting pain to answer.
- 留言即可 - 他就这么一个任务
- Leave a message - This guy got one job.
找到初刃然后把它拿回来
Find the first blade,bring it back.
- 到底有多难 - 那可是Crowley
- How hard is that - Yeah,that's Crowley.
他可不善于团队合作
He is not exactly a team player.
是啊 但是他自己也不惜一切代价
Yeah,but his ass is on the line,too.
一周不见人影可能吗
He goes missing for a week without a peep.
我只是想知道原因
Well,now I wanna make sense anyway.
听听这个
Listen to this.
Dean
Dean.
等一下
Wait a sec.
他这是喝醉了给你打电话吗
Did he drunk dial you.
非麋鹿
Not Moose.
Lola
Lola.
我的国王
My king.
我的航空保鲜美食
My air pri consummation treat.
这就去
On it.
血基本上放空了
Pantry's almost empty.
我们需要一个新的志愿者
We will need another volunteer.
你应该把这条加在清单列表里
You should add that on your to-do-list.
Lola 亲爱的
Lola,pet.
我天性贪婪
I do believe I'm ravenous.
我是Elgo
My name is Elgo.
消息是给Abaddon的
My intell's for Abaddon.
- 狗奴才 - 她很欣赏你的工作
- Minion - And she appreciates the works you've been doing.
- 原来是只八哥啊 - 但是她忙于建设
- A great parrot - But she's tied up securing her places.
自己的新王国
As the new leader of the kingdom.
她向你保证所以的相关信息
She assures you that all relavent imformation.
都可以告诉我
Can be conveyed to me.
说吧
So,update.
地狱之王已经没有胜算了
The king is off his game.
除了性爱 披萨和人血 他对其他的都不感兴趣
Except for sex pizza and human blood,he has no interests.
他已经离不开我了
He can't function without me.
- 干得漂亮 - 还有
- Well played - I should mention.
Winchester兄弟不断的给他打电话
He keeps getting phone calls from those Winchesters.
他们给他留语音
They leave voice mails for him.
说了什么
Saying.
大部分都是骂人的
Mostly they are rude.
有一次提到了叫做初刃的东西
One mentioned something called the first blade.
有意思
Interesting.
看紧事情进展 有情况就汇报
Follow how this developes and report it.
我会的
Oh I will.
但是我希望
And when I do.
能直接向下一任地狱女王汇报
I expect to report directly to the next queen of hell.
懂了吗
Capisce.
来吧
All right, do it
[咒语]
Winchester兄弟
Winchesters.
她是不是
Is that a.
没错 这能解释很多
Well,that explains a lot.
好吧听着 Snooki 我能这么叫你吗
Okay,look,Snooki,can I call you Snooki.
不 我现在叫Nicole
No,it's Nicole now.
那好吧 Nicole
Okay,then,Nicole.
现在有两种解决方法
Look,we can do this one out of two ways.
简单的 你乖乖讲真话
The easy way,you talk.
或者
Or.
更简单的
The easier way.
你乖乖说实话
You still talk.
我个人偏向第二种
I vote for number two.
我们只是想要点儿
We just want some basic information.
Crolwey的消息罢了
On Crowley,that's it.
问谷歌 行了吧
Google it.Are we done.
别打脸 你有病啊
Wow,not the face,are you crazy.
听着 地狱里的事儿不会到处乱跑
Listen,guys,what happens in hell stays in hell.
我什么都不知道
I got nothing.
有Crowley称王的时候
Yeah,but don't you have a pretty sweet deal.
你们都有好差事可做
When Crowley in charge.
如果Abaddon上位
If Abaddon wins.
情况可就不会这么好了
You can kiss all that goodbye.
没有炫酷的跑车 没有打折的好书
All the fancy cars,the book deal.
没活儿干的日子可不轻松
Short of business can be tough.
我现在生意挺好的 谢谢关心
I'm doing fine,thanks.
真不巧 你这次现身在了恶魔陷阱里
Oh,good luck landing inside a devil's trap.
你们想知道什么
What do you want to know.
Crowley在哪儿
Where's Crowley.
最后一次有他的消息
Last time I heard,he was somewhere.
他正在太平洋西部乱搞
In the western pacific.
还真有可能
Make sense.
别搞笑了
Really.
他的领土都乱成一锅粥了
Fooling around in the ocean.
他还有心情看海
While his kingdom goes up in flames.
你什么意思
Meaning.
地狱现在情况非常不好
Hell's getting crazy.
就连昔日的死党们都想倒向Abaddon了
Even the loyalists wanna assigned on with Abaddon.
她动作不小
She's gotta make her move.
完事儿了没 我还有点儿私事儿
Are we done, I got a thing
[咒语]
真的吗 你要驱逐我 我们刚做了个交易
Seriously?An exorcism?We had a deal.
回见了 Snooks
See ya,Snooks.
小妇人 Meg Jo Beth和Amy
Little Women.Meg,Jo,Beth and Amy.
作者Louisa M Alcott
Written by Louisa M Alcott.
甜心 我回来了
Honey,I'm home.
你好呀 小南瓜
Hello,Pumkin.
今天过得怎么样
Did you have a nice day.
Lola去购物了
Lola did some shopping.
看起来Lola买的东西还不少
Looks like Lola did a lot of shopping.
不全都是给我自己买的
But not all of it is for me.
看呐 看呐
Looky,looky.
希望口感不错
I hope it's a good vintage.
看起来配着点儿酒一起喝会更好
Well you look like you could use a little pick-me-up.
我喜欢你喝醉之后的样子
I just love what it does for you.
是吗
Do you.
跟我斗
You try to play me.
我才是老大
I play the tune.
其他人都必须按着我的规则来
Everyone else dances to it.
- 明白了吗 - 明白了
- Got it? - Yes.
我是你的奴隶
I'm your slave.
你是我的小老鼠
You're my rodent.
我那个跑到Abaddon跟前
My little rodent until when scarring off to Abaddon.
去告我状的小老鼠
To rat on me.
不 不
No,no.
你真觉得其他人
Do you really think some other low life.
不会出卖你吗
Wouldn't sell you out.
我本来以为你是个聪明的好女孩
I thought you were a smart girl.
我本来能帮你的
A girl I could've helped.
开什么玩笑
You're joking right.
你帮我
You help me.
看看你自己
Look at yourself.
你谁都帮不了
You couldn't help anyone
马里亚纳大海沟
The Mariana Trench.
嘿
Hey.
之前
So.
Cain说初刃被藏在
Cain said that the first blade.
海的最深处
Was tossed into the deepest ocean.
说不定就是马里亚纳大海沟
That's the Mariana Trench.
说不定Crowley早就找到初刃了
Maybe Crowley found it.
只不过在骗我们玩儿
And it's a double cross.
没有道理啊
That doesn't make sense.
他想让我得到初刃 去杀了Abaddon
He wants me to power up and kill that ginger.
这都是他的主意
He set it up.
好吧 假设他真的把初刃带过来
OK,assuming he does show up with it.
我们拿到初刃之后 Crowley就没用了
Crowley is only useful to us until we have the blade.
是啊 所以呢
Yeah,so.
所以
So.
我们也可以反过来利用他
There's nothing stopping us from using it on him.
对吧
Right.
完全可以
Nothing at all.
说曹操曹操到
Speak to devil.
你找到初刃了吗
Did you find the first blade.
还不算
Not exactly.
那你是什么情况
Well then what exactly.
我现在有点儿小麻烦
I'm in a jam I thought.
你们应该能帮得上忙
Thought you might help.
好呀 孩子们
Hello,boys.
你管这个叫什么
And what do you call this.
饭后甜点
Refreshments.
- 袋子里装的是什么 Crowley - 没什么
- What's in the package Crowley - Nothing.
真的吗 那我看看
Really,maybe I can.
你怎么搞的 抢劫了血库吗
What are you...knocking over blood banks.
别这样
Come on guys.
看看你自己 像什么样子
Look at you,you're a mess.
你知道我们都指着你呢
You know we were counting on you.
你让我们失望了
You let us down.
你那帮地狱狗腿子也都指望着你
Your slimy followers were counting.
干掉Abaddon呢
On you to kill Abaddon.
你让他们失望了
You let them down.
最厉害的恶魔 邪恶之王
The man with all the mojo.Captain Evil.
真可悲
That's pathetic.
这算什么
What is this.
劝说大会吗
An intervention.
你需要集中精力 Crowley
You need to focus,Crowley.
认真一点儿
Get a grip.
你是打算让地狱见鬼去吗
What you are just gonna let the hell go to hell.
你根本不知道做人的滋味
You don't know what it's like to be human.
汝之血
It's your DNA.
吾之瘾
It's my addiction.
也就是我的负担
My cross.My burden.
行 放松点
All right,take it easy.
我现在知道这种瘾有多恐怖了
I see the darkness of it now.
比政治还恐怖
The Anthony Weiner of it.
那种永远填不满的欲望
Makes you needy.
我需要Lola
I needed her.
但她利用了我
Lola used me.
她把知道的都通报给Abaddon
She reported everything I did back to Abaddon.
Crowley
Crowley.
她知道初刃吗
Did you tell her about the first blade.
我不知道
I don't know.
嗑上药之后记不住事情
Things get a trifle blurry when I'm medicaid.
这下可好
Great.
Lola知道了一定会告诉Abaddon
If he told Lola,she definitely told Abaddon.
所以Abaddon也在寻找初刃
Which means that Abaddon's in the hunt of this thing,too.
我告诉你 你现在这状态立刻换掉
All right,you know what?This crap ends now.
现在这样子立刻终止 明白了吗
You're cut off.Okay.
戒掉
Kicking it.Cold turkey.
又回到老地方了
Back in this fetid pit.
连枕头都不给
Could at least have added some throw pillows.
集中注意力
Focus.Okay.
你搜过了马里亚纳海沟 然后呢
You swept Mariana's trench,and.
出乎意料的是 初刃不在那儿
And the first blade was not as hoped in the trench.
很早以前就被一艘无人驾驶的潜水艇捞上来了
That in fact had been scooped up by an unmanned sub.
然后被一个研究助理偷走了
From whom it was stolen by research assistant.
之后又卖给了葡萄牙走私贩
Who reportedlly sold it to Portuguese smugglar.
他打牌的时候输给了摩洛哥海盗
Who in turn lost it to Moroccan pirates in a poker game.
什么
What.
可怜的鹿鹿
Poor moose.
跟上我的思路不太容易 对吧
It's always a little tricky keeping up isn't it.
你看什么
What are you doing.
我被人性玷污了而已
I'm still a little tainted by humanity.
略伤感
Makes me sentimental.
够了
Well,stop.
你我都知道去年教堂里发生了什么
You and I both know we shared a mo back in that church.
某种程度上说 我们是一体的
On some level,we are bonded.
Crowley 你知道你为什么还活着吗
Crowley.The only reason you are alive.
因为要你帮我们除掉Abaddon
Is that we need your help to deel with Abaddon.
比起她 你还不算彻底的混蛋
Cause she is the even worse pile of crap than you are.
我对你就这么点怜惜
And that's the extent of my concerns for you.
懂了吗
Got it.
海盗之后发生了什么
Okay.What happened after the pirates.
他在干什么
What is Crowley doing.
偷糖
Stealing candies.
他 呃 他 他在偷糖
He is..He He's stealing candies.
至少Cass变成人的时候
You know,at least when Cass was human.
是个正常人
He was an okay guy.
早该想到Crowley就是个混混
Should've known Crowley would be a douche version.
喂 说你呢
Hey!Hey.
别乱来了行吗 注意形象
Cut it out man.Image.
你是地狱之王 有个王的样子
You are the king of rotten,act like one.
你觉得那家伙会来吗
Do you really think this guy's gonna show up.
我看不像会有人愿意在这里
I mean this isn't exactly a place.
做几百万的交易
Where a million dollar's deal go down.
听着 传言说 这个叫André Develin的人
Look.Word is this André Develin character.
从海盗手里买下初刃
Bought the blade from the pirates,and he's.
到处拿着卖 我就知道这么多
Been shopping it around.That's all I know.
注意 来人了
Hey,heads up.
Devilon先生 我们打过电话
Mr.Devilon We spoke on the phone.
你之前说你代表一个正经的买家
You said you represent a serious collector.
想通过私下交易的方式来交货
With an interest in a private transaction.
是吗
Did he.
哦 是吗 其实他的意思是
Oh,well.What he meant to say was.
我们是FBI的人
That we are with the FBI.
祝你们晚安
Then good evening.
等等 我们只想打探一下消息
Wait a second.We just want some answers.
Read Sartre
Read Sartre.
Jean-Paul Sartre
Jean-Paul Sartre.
我只是帮买家和卖家牵线而已
I'm merely a fascilitator between the buyer.
干中间人买卖
And the seller,a conduit.
除非你们要拘留我
So unless I'm been detained.
请问是吗
So am I.
请问我被拘留了吗
Been detained.
目前没有
Not at the moment.
没 但我们会时刻留意你的
No.But we've got our eyes on you.
国家文物研究所
National Institute of Antiquties.
炸弹 又赢了
Gin.Again.
给你们带了点吃的东西
Brought you guys something for your shift.
怎么了
What's going on.
我也没发现什么特别的
I don't have much for you guys.
这两个保安都是好人
Guards are good men.
在这儿工作好几年了
They'd been here for years.
按时上班 老实巴交
Vetted,honest.
- 但是 - 但是什么
- But - But.
监视录像拍到 助理研究员
Security camera shows a reaserch assistant caught them.
撞见他们打开1号保险库
Breaking into vault number one.
就是她吗
That's her.
更奇怪了不是吗
Gets weirder.
跟我之前说的一样
Like I said.
那个保险库里有什么特别的东西吗
Anything special about the paticular vault they opened.
1号保险库是
Vault number one is.
储存新到的文物
Where they keep rare and new acquisitions.
还在接受鉴定
While they are being examined.
被偷的是哪一件
So what was stolen.
重点就在这 什么都没丢
That's a kicker Nothing.
馆长McIlroy博士说
The curator Doctor McIlroy said.
这个保险库已经空了几个星期了
The vault's been empty for weeks.
探员 打扰一下
Excuse me,detective.
我们来理一下思路
Okay,so just connect the dots here.
他们刚来的时候
The blade was likely put in there.
初刃很可能被放在这里
When they first got here.
然后保安被附身了
The guards are obviously demons,so.
然后 发现是空的 没有初刃
What,when the vault turned out to be empty.
就杀了这两个皮囊 然后跑了
They killed their guard meat suits and smoked out.
去向谁汇报
And reported back to who.
Abaddon吗
Abaddon.
她就在附近
She's closing in.
也就是说初刃从来没有展出过
So the first blade was never on display.
研究所没有认证过
No authenticated item by that name.
初刃这种东西
Was ever on this premises.
认证
Authenticated.
McElroy博士 这把匕首被
Dr.McElroy,this blade was stolen.
偷运进美国已经违反了
And smuggled into the US in violation of treaties.
多国法律
With several governments.
我们可以强迫你开口
We can compel you to speak.
强迫
Compel.
具体怎么强迫
And what might that involve.
好吧好吧
All right,look.
我确实拿回来这个叫初刃的匕首
I did acquire this so called first blade.
碳14测定确认该物属圣经时代
And carbon dating did peg it to biblical times.
但是权威认证却不这么说
But the authentication proved unreliable.
所以之前确实在保险库里
So it was in the vault.
我把它拿出去了
I removed it myself.
- 保安不知道 - 现在在哪儿
- The guards didn't know - Where is it now.
几周前
Several weeks ago.
一个神秘买家出价要买
A confidential offer was made to purchase it.
我害怕永远过不了权威认证那关 所以
I was afraid we would never authenticate the thing,so.
买家是谁
Who was the buyer.
不好意思
Sorry.
买家要求信息绝对保密
The buyer insisted on absolute secrecy.
不好意思 联邦法律刚好挡住了
Well,federal statutes trump your little deal.
买家信息
So,the buyer.
不管怎么样 你是都要知道的
And you'll get it out of me one way or another.
对不对 探员
Won't you, Agent.
我从来不知道他的真实身份
I never did know his real identity.
他自称Magnus
He called himself Magnus.
别问我他住在哪里 我也不知道
Don't ask me where he lives I have no idea.
我还有个会
But I do have a meeting,so.
这是我的号码 如果你们还需要帮助
Here is my number,should you need anything else.
怎么了
What.
你听到她说的了吗 Magnus
Did you catch that Magnus.
Albert Magnus
Albert Magnus.
学者们想要销声匿迹的时候
The name the Men of Letters used.
用的化名
When they want to be incognito.
是的 但是所有的学者都死了
Yeah,but we know that all of the Men of Letters are dead.
确定吗
Do we.
夜床服务吗
Turndown service.
请在我枕头上放块薄荷
I'd like a mint on my pillow.
关于1958年的学者大屠杀
What do you know about.
你都知道些什么
The Men of Letters massacre of 1958.
我们知道Larry Ganem
We know Abaddon missed.
和我们的祖父从Abaddon手下逃生
Our grandfather and Larry Ganem.
还有别人活下来了吗
Was there anybody else.
我就有话直说了
Let me get this straight.
你把我关在这个柜子里
You keep me locked up in this closet.
对我的痛苦不闻不问
Ignore my suffering.
然后来这里讨价还价 要求我帮助你们
And then come barging in here and demand my help.
差不多吧
More or less,yeah.
上一次我不是
Did I or did I not.
所有忙都帮完了
Keep my end of the bargain the other night.
帮得还非常漂亮
Quite brilliantly,I might add.
我们可是搭档
We are partners.
你们欠我个人情
And you owe me.
- 还欠你 - 如果不是为了你们
- Owe you - I wouldn't be in this mess.
我也不会身陷麻烦之中
If it wasn't for you two.
你们抓了我
You shoot me up.
把我变成了瘾君子
You make me a junkie.
你们一藏把我藏好几个月
You keep me stashed away for months.
同时间里我的王国都快崩塌了
While my kingdom falls apart.
你想要什么
What do you want.
这苏格兰威士忌可不怎么样
It's not a very good scotch,is it.
Crowley 我们已经翻遍了
Okay,Crowley,we have gone through the records.
1958年全部的人员名单
For the entire membership in 1958.
每个名字都能和死人中的一个对上号
Every single name matches the men who were killed.
是的 那只是一线活跃人员名单 对吗
That would be the active membership,correct.
你们俩个是不是脑子出问题了
Were you two dropped on your heads a great deal.
我告诉过你们的 有消息说
Like I told you,rumor has it.
有个笨蛋因为他的愚蠢行为被开除了
That a rogue member was tossed out on his arse.
这还能活跃在一线吗
That make him active.
说真的 孩子们 离了我你们怎么活啊
Seriously,boys,how did you ever function without me.
你好啊 Ichigatsu小姐
Well,hello,Miss Ichigatsu.
Infamati et obliterati
Infamati et obliterati.
羞耻即被遗忘
Dishonored and forgotten.
哇
Wow.
这家伙真与众不同
This guy was something.
- 好拗口的名字 - 嗯 Cuthbert Sinclair
- Tough name - Yeah,Cuthbert Sinclair.
我还是喜欢Magnus
I'd have just gone with Magnus.
看起来是他设计了大部分的防御系统
Looks like he designed most of the warding.
来保护地堡的安全
That keeps the bunker safe.
这里说他被称为咒语大师
Says here that he was named Master of Spells.
就在他发起这个之后
Right after he initiated it.
似乎他的研究后来发展得有点疯狂
I guess his work got a little crazy.
他被形容为怪异的和不负责任的
The leadership called it eccentric and irresponsible.
很好 这些是他在这儿的
Good,so these are the projects that.
最后几年里 提出的课题
He proposed in the last of years he was here.
看看这些
Look at this.
否决 否决 否决
Rejected,rejected,rejected.
太困难了
So difficult.
一代英才 生不逢时 被其蔑视
Brilliant,ahead of your time,dispised for it.
相信我 我深有体会
Trust me.I know.
正式脱离学者组织是在
Formal separation from Man of Letters.
1956年4月
April 1956.
刚好错过了那场屠杀
He missed the massacre.
我一直不知道他叫什么
I never knew his name.
但是我知道有人避过了
But I heard someone was out.
费了好大劲也没找到
Did my damnest to find him.
我觉得他也许是我了解这个契合点的方法
Thought he might be my way inside this joint.
那么 你找到了哪里
So where did you look.
这就是你的手下们跟踪到他的地方
So this is where your demons tracked him to.
没错
Exact spot.
我的手下一直找不到他
My boys could never find him.
我什么都没感觉到
I'm sensing nothing.
如果他在这里的话
So if he's here.
他就是被这些沟壑防御起来了
He's warded up to the gills.
他是这方面的天才 对吧
Well,he's a genius at it,right.
肯定知道怎样不被恶魔找到
Sure as hell ain't gonna be found by a bunch of demons.
说得像他会向你们吐露心声一样
Like he's gonna open his heart to you lot.
因为你们是宝藏
Because you are such prizes.
比这还要好 我们是传人
Better,we are legacies.
如果他藏在这里的话
All right,if he's so bent on hiding.
可能他看得到我们
Maybe he's watching.
试试吧
Give it a shot.
Cuthbert Sinclair还是Magnus 随便你叫什么
Cuthbert Sinclair,Magnus,whatever.
我们是Sam和Dean Winchester
We are Sam and Dean Winchester.
Henry Winchester的孙子
Henry Winchester's grandsons.
我们也是学者
And Man of Letters ourselves.
我们知道之前发生了什么
We know what happened back in the day.
我们并不赞成你的做法
We don't necessarily agree with it.
我们想
We figured.
也许你想给我们讲讲你眼中的事实
Maybe you want to tell your side of the story.
往哪边走
Which way.
真棒 干得漂亮
Bravo.Well done.
真抱歉 刚才来那么一出
Sorry about all these theatricality.
我只是想看看你们到底是什么做的
I just wanted to see what you two were made of.
我们是在地下吗
So,what,are we underground.
不 你们站的地方就是我堡垒的所在地
No,my fortress was where you were standing.
不过 它是隐形的
But,it's invisible.
你一定就是Curthbert Sinclair
Then you must be Cuthbert Sinclair.
我没用那个名字
I haven't done by that moniker in.
已经57年了
57 years now.
对于一个快90岁的人来说 你看起来不错
You are looking good for a guy pushing 90.
谢了 小子
Well,thanks,sport.
几乎没有什么事是咒语办不到的
There's a spell for damn near everything.
但是你们让我印象深刻
I'm impressed though.
你们正好做到了你们该做的
You did exactly what you should have done.
虽然 我还是会想念我怪兽动物园中的那两只
Though I'm gonna miss those two from my zoo.
你的怪兽动物园
Your zoo.
先生们
Oh,gentlemen.
你们正身处
You are in the mist of.
世界上最伟大的超自然
The greatest collection of supernatural rarities.
收藏馆中
And antiquities on the planet.
对不起 你们是不是说你们是学者
I'm sorry.Did you say that you are the man of letters.
我以为1958之后就没那个组织了
I thought that whole thing's dead after '58.
我们 我们是传人
We are,we are legacies.
但是 事实上 我们是猎人
But,actually,we are hunters.
猎人
Hunters.
猎人 手握着王国的钥匙
Hunters,with the key to the kingdom.
那些死学者们肯定在坟墓里高兴地起舞了
Boys must be spinning in their graves.
势利小人们 要我说 他们就是一群图书管理员
Damn snobs,bunch of librarians if you ask me.
不过 我一直很喜欢Henry
Although,I was always found of Henry.
我是他的导师
I was his mentor,you know.
直到那群老家伙给我穿小鞋
Yeah,till the squares gave me the boot.
当然 他也来拜访过我 秘密地
Of course,he came here to visit me,in secret.
也是像你们这样呼喊我
Called out to me the same way you did.
哦 对 离你们的祖父来这里已经有一些时候了
Oh,yes,quite a while here your grandfather was.
听着 Magnus 我们现在有一个状况
Listen,Magnus,we got ourselves a situation.
Abaddon 最后一个地狱骑士
Abaddon,the last knight of hell.
正在试图夺权
Is looking to up her pay grade and take over the place.
事情真是一成不变
Things never change,do they.
我之前一遍遍地告诉他们
I kept telling the boys over and over again.
我说 我们可以阻止这一切
I would say,we could stop all this.
我们可以一次性消灭
We could rid of the monsters.
世界上所有的怪物
In the world once and for all.
如果我们能用心的话 但是他们说不
If we just put our minds to it,but oh no,they said.
这不是我们的任务
No,no,no,it's not our place.
我们是来做研究的 做分类整理工作的
We're here to study.We are here to catalogue.
我们明白 他们是书呆子
Yeah,we get it.They were geeks.
但是我们可以阻止她
But she can be stopped.
你有我们需要的东西
But we need something we hear you have.
初刃
The first blade.
我明白了
I see.
有意思
Interesting.
但是如果你们真的做足了功课的话
But if you'd really done your homework.
你们就知道初刃根本没有用
You would know that it's absolutely useless.
除非你们有
Unless of course you are possessing the.
- 一个印记 - 该隐之印
- Mark - The mark of Cain.
天啊
Oh my.
你怎么弄到这个的
How did you come by that.
听着 如果Abaddon掌权
Listen,If Abaddon takes over.
她最想做的一件事
The one thing she wants more than anything.
就是将人间变为地狱
Is to make hell on earth.
就算是你也逃不了
Not even you can escape that.
人们都说猎人都是蠢货
And they say all hunters are morons.
就在你们身后 先生们
It's right there behind you,gentlemen.
如果你刚说的采取行动的话是认真的
Listen,if you are serious about taking actions.
这就是我们在采取行动
This...This is taking action.
你借我们初刃 我们去阻止那个贱人
You loan us that blade and we will stop the bitch.
我来考虑一下
Let me think about it.
好的 我想好了
All right,I thought about it.
Magnus和Dean在一起
Magnus has Dean.
你对我弟弟做了什么
What did you do with my brother.
别担心 他没事
Don't worry.He's fine.
但是我做了所有伟大的收藏家都会做的事
But I did what any good collector would do.
把平凡的
I separate the ordinary.
和非凡的分开
From the extraordinary.
我有初刃
I had the first blade.
现在 我也有了该隐之印来完成
Now,I have the Mark of Cain to complete the set.
问题是 该隐之印和我是一体的
Well,the problem is it's attached.
你把初刃给我
So how about you loan me the blade.
我来完成这些怎么样
And I take care of the business.
Dean 我给你的是再好不过选择了
Dean,I'm offering you the moon here.
可以成为史上最伟大的收藏的一部分
To be part of the greatest collection of all time.
永葆青春
To be young forever.
我来告诉你我的秘密吧
Let me teach you my secrets.
来陪我吧
Be my companion.
老实说
I have to be honest with you.
这些年来 我有些寂寞了
It has gotten lonely here over the years.
你说这话的时候
When you were saying any of that.
有没有觉得有些诡异
Did it feel at all creep.
现在 我就拿着刀直接离开了
Now,I'm just gonna grab the blade and go.
这个地方有个设计缺陷
One little design flaw of the place.
没有窗户 没有门
No windows,no doors.
这样的话
Well,in that case.
我只好自己动手了
I'll just make my own.
挺不错的小咒语吧
Tricky little spell that first one,right.
中国来的
Chinese.
小魔术师的手段
Cheap magician's trick on that one.
摸兜
Picked your pocket.
枪不错
Nice gun.
欢迎成为收藏品的一员 Dean
Welcome to the collection,Dean.
想试试吗
You mind.
谁能想到呢
Who would have think it,moose.
你和我 同一战线 同一战壕
You and me,same team,in the trenches.
完事之后 我们可以弄个情侣纹身
When this is over we can get matching tattoos.
我要澄清一点 Crowley
All right,just to be clear,Crowley.
我们什么都站不到一起
We are not on the same,anything.
顺便说一句 既然这个地方已经被咒语保护了
By the way,since the place is warded.
你的功力也发挥不了了
Your powers are useless.
也就是说 你比平常更没用了
Which means you are useless,even more so than usual.
你进去的时候
You are gonna need another set of hands.
肯定需要帮手的
When you get in there.
除非你已经有了其他的志愿者人选
Unless you have the volunteers in mind.
谢谢 不用了
Thanks,pass.
如果我没记错的话
Memory serves me.
是我帮你哥找到了Cain
I am the one who helped your brother find Cain.
然后我们才找到了初刃
So that we can find the blade.
再之后Dean才收到了印记
So that Dean could receive the mark.
是我把Gadreel
I'm the one who flashed out loud that Gadreel.
从你身上扯出来的
Out of your nogging.
所以 孩子
So,lately,big boy.
最近我的贡献比你多
I'e served more playing time than you.
Crwoley 你能不能闭上该死的嘴
Crowley,will you please shut the hell up.
你还真是一个小可怜
Oh you're a really sorry piece of work you know that.
窝在这里 什么都不做
Holed up in here,doing nothing.
你还说学者的不是
You bitching about men of letters.
你可差远了
You're way worse.
来试试
Should we fire it up.
你觉得怎样
What do you say.
去死吧
Go to hell.
别这样 Dean
Oh,come on,Dean.
这不就是你要找的东西吗
This is the object of your quest.
告诉我 Henry Winchester的孙儿
Tell me,Henry Winchester's grandson.
不想知道这东西管不管用
Isn't curious to see if it works.
把手给我
Give me your hand.
手 给我
这就对了
That's it.
好极了
Good.
下次会更顺畅
Next time it'll be easier.
你会习惯的 甚至会喜欢这感觉
You'll get used to the feelings,even welcome them.
看这个
Here's something.
显然 他想将整个学者基地
Apparently,he wanted to make the entire.
变成隐形的
Men of letters' bunker invisible.
所有物理实物的入口都会被封锁
All physical points of entry were to be eliminated.
唯一的进入方法是
And entrance would only be gained.
咒语
By spell.
看来我们需要点东西
We're gonna need some things.
你可能真的能派上用场了 Crowley
You actually might turn out to be useful,Crowley.
你会明白的Dean
You'll come to understand,Dean.
没有什么可以阻挡我们
Nothing can stop us.
任何东西 任何人
Anything,anyone we want to.
只要我们想要或者摧毁的 都逃不掉
Own or destroy is ours.
好吧 那这样如何 Magnus
Well,how about this,Magnus.
假如我不肯这么干呢
How about I take a knee.
那你会怎么做
Then what are you gonna do.
杀了我吗
Huh?You gonna kill me.
因为假如没有我胳膊上的印记
Cause without this thing on my arm.
那把刀就只是块带牙齿的骨头
That Blade's nothing but a hunk of bone with teeth.
我并不是在征求你的同意
Well,I'm not asking you for your cooperation.
我会直接来拿
I'm just taking it.
感觉很有趣吧
Interesting effect.
所有的思想和意愿都
All thought,all will just.
从你身体里被吸干了
Drained out of you.
我干这个早就干够了
I do this enough.
现在无论我想要你做什么 你都会立刻准备好
You'll be ready for whatever I have in mind.
我做的不错吧 麋鹿
I did good,moose.
单子上的东西都齐了
Everything on the list.
不用谢啊
You're welcome.
记住 跟紧
Remember,stay close.
按我说的做
Do what I say.
什么都不许说
Shut the hell up.
抱着就行了 对吧
I'm growing on you,aren't I.
真喜欢他重新装修的风格
Love what he has done to this place.
带我去找我哥
Take me to my brother.
Sam 别
Sam,no.
变形怪
Shapeshifer.
看到了吧 这就是开怪兽动物园的好处
You see?There are benefit to keeping a zoo.
知道吗
You know.
我对你太早下定论了
I discarded you far too quickly,Sam.
你比我想象的还要有价值
You are way more valuable than I thought you were.
我为什么要装着被你制服了
Why would I knock myself out.
来降低你的警惕性呢
Trying to sap your will.
我手里有了Sam 就能让你
I think Sam here can get you.
更好的理解我是怎么想的
To see things in my way.
Magnus我发誓
Magnus I swear to God.
怎么 你能怎么样
What?What're you gonna do.
他能怎么样
What is he gonna do.
听着 Sam 我不会杀你
Look,look,Sam,I'm not gonna kill you.
我为什么要杀你呢 但是
Of course not.But.
我会让你尝到无法想象的痛苦
I'm gonna make you suffer unimaginably.
Dean
Dean.
结束了
Hey,it's over.
他死了
He's dead.
把刃放下 Dean
Drop the blade,Dean.
Dean
Dean.
把刃放下
Drop the blade.
我必须说 真是太棒了
Brilliant,I must say.
当然是说我自己
Speaking of myself of course.
你们俩永远是被绑起来挨揍的料
All you two manage to do is to get trussed up.
有了我的大无畏行动
Combining a little derring-do on my part.
加上松鼠的蛮力
A little dumb muscle from squirrel.
和麋鹿的几滴血
A little bleeding from moose.
欢乐大结局 放片尾职员表
Happy ending,roll credits.
我去 搞什么
No,no,no!Come on.
怎么回事
What the hell.
硫磺 恶魔
Sulfur,demons.
Abaddon的
Abaddon's.
她比我们慢了一步
She just one jump behind us.
估计也是找不着Magnus
Guess she couldn't find Magnus' joint either.
后备箱怎么样
What about the trunk.
后备箱没事
Safe.
保护咒没让他们得逞
Warding kept them out.
恶魔混蛋竟然动我宝贝
Demon mitts all over my baby.
靠
Come on.
还敢刮花
Now they're keying cars.
那是什么语
What language is that.
天使语
It's Enochian.
不是留给你们的
The message isn't for you.
是给我的
It's for me.
吓到尿裤子吧 女王陛下留
Be afraid,Your queen.
Abaddon是越来越厚脸皮了
Abaddon's getting more brazen.
她觉得我不行了
She thinks I'm losing my grip.
Dean
Dean.
听着
Listen.
你说过 找到初刃之后Crowley就没用了
You said Crowley was only useful till we got the blade.
现在初刃找到了
We got the blade.
话说 孩儿们啊
You know,boys.
我欠你们一次
I'm in debt to you.
是你们帮我戒了人血
You forced sobriety on me.
现在我总算看清楚了
Now I can see the situation for what it is.
Dean 你还真是个厉害的杀戮机器
Dean,you are quite the killing machine.
我突然想到
And it occurs to me that.
Abaddon不是唯一在你死亡名单上的名字
Abaddon is not the only name on your list.
我自己恐怕也是榜上有名
My name,must be up there as well.
没有我 你拿着它也没用
It's no good to you without me.
说的是 但是只要我拿着
Yes,but as long as I have it.
对你也没用
It's no good to you.
现在 事情是这样的
Now this is the way it's going to go.
这老古董我拿着
I'll hang on to old donkey teeth here.
直到你能找到Abaddon
Until such time as you locate Abaddon.
然后你就能灭了她了
Then you'll destroy her.
麋鹿你之前说的对
You're right moose.
你们不能信任我
You can't trust me.
遗憾的是 我也不能信任你们
Sadly, I can't trust you either